This is Libre, speaking directly from Gaza City.
As we go into October 7th, it is the right of indigenous people to protect their land under international law from illegal occupation.
That includes the Palestinians, and so they have a right to resistance.
As we go into the second year of the genocide here in Gaza, we haven't been able to sleep.
There's still non-stop bombing. In the last few days, there's been well over 150 different bombings throughout Gaza.
As the Western media outlets try to detract people by saying that there's a ceasefire, there's ceasefire talks, or the Israelis aren't bombing, that's a lie.
Don't believe them. They continue to massacre indiscriminately the people here in Gaza City.
And this is all connected. We need to continue to uplift things.
October 6th, 1996, the first genocide in East Congo started.
There's also a genocide happening in Sudan.
So there's three genocides happening right now that the Zionists are all involved in for Congo.
It has to do with Dan Gerbler, a billionaire Zionist that exploits the people of Congo through cobalt mining, as well as gold and diamonds.
And it's the same thing with Sudan, with the gold.
Did you know that 40% of Israel's capital comes from the Congo?
So everything literally is connected.
There's a Zionist billionaire in Haiti that is helping to create the chaos that is creating the instability in IAT,
the first revolution that we should always respect.
And the Reuben brothers are two Zionists that are in the process of building Proyecto Esencia in Puerto Rico, in Borinque,
a project that is illegally stealing federally protected land.
And the government of Puerto Rico, the governor Jennifer Gonzalez, is working with tech bros and the Zionists.
She's a staunch Zionist and Zionist supporter.
There's also the continued military exercises the U.S. is doing as it continues to commit illegal acts by attacking the sovereignty of the Republic of Venezuela.
Venezuela, and they have killed up to now 21 people illegally.
Chile is in the process of declassifying documents that connect Israel directly to La Guerra Sucia in Chile,
which means they were also involved not only in Chile, but Argentina,
as well as the massacre of indigenous people in Central America.
So literally this is all connected.
So we need to continue to plan strategic unified actions to end this genocide
because it's connected to all of the other things that are happening that are being led by imperialism and Zionism.